Hello everyone, welcome back to our post gray SQL tutorial series, so today we are going to explore
how to create the tables in the post gray SQL. This is a fundamental aspect of the database
management. Okay, first of all, the segment for understanding the post gray SQL pure table statement.
So first of all, we can create a table in the post gray SQL is a
precious step in the designing the database schema and the table will be find the structure of
the table for the data including the column and there data type. Okay, so now let's explore
how it works with some example. Okay, so here in this session, I will again use for the SQL
server management studio and apply for the post gray SQL data query. Okay, so now
the start. So first of all, the first example is starting with the
data component table with the ID as a primary key and not null and concepts showing the field
cannot be null while creating the record in that table. Okay, so now just go ahead and first of all,
here I can create the table. Okay, so this is the create table and use for the table name
supposed like this companion. Okay, and here I can create the parentheses and in this inside,
I can insert for some column information. So first of all, I can type the ID.
Okay, so ID, this is the integer for the call the primary key. Okay, and here I can define this
the not null. So next step, I can also create the main column. So name, this will be the text. Okay,
and this is the not null. Okay, and then I can also place this is the edge column. So edge,
this integer type and both the not null. Okay, and the system for another column, this will be
the address. Okay, so a double D, or a double S address, and here address this, the character type,
and here values for the character of 15. Okay, and also we're going to create the salary column.
So the salary, and this is the real. Okay, so here completely create, this is the new table
for the companion table. And now just here, I can select an execute, and I can expect for
the confirmation message, show by in the display. Okay, so I can select and then execute,
and you can see here, the command is completely successful, and here create, show the message for the
command is completely successful. Okay, so I hope you understand it, and now let us create the
more table, and we will use our exercise in the sequential chapter. So here, I can create another
table, and now just go for the new query open, and first of all, just type for pure table,
a statement. So table stem, just like the department. Okay,
so define perfectly. So here, at the parenthesis, and inside, I can create for the,
suppose like first of all, I can type the enter, die, this is the primary key. Okay,
and here, not none. And the next step here, I can create this, the depth. Okay,
so depth for DC is a character type, and here, inside the character is 50, and here,
it is both the not null, and now, we can create also for define, so it is here first,
we can use ID, then the integer. Okay, so this is perfect, and here, create for the employee's ID,
so first of all, the ID. So this is the integer type for the not null. Okay, so now here,
completely defined, and here, I can click the onboard table, and here, now, I can select, and
here, it is perfectly selected for the new department table, and completely created. Now, okay,
so now, just there, I can select and execute, and you can see here, this command is completely
successful, because in this department table, completely created. Okay, and you can verify for
here, use for perfectly created this table, and has been created successfully,
and you can use the command, and this will be used to list down the table
in the database. Okay, so now, just verify the stride, so here, I can create another new query,
and first of all, here, just type the keyword select, Mr, from here, create the companion
table, okay, and put the semicolon and just select all, and then execute, and you can see here,
perfectly prepared for the ID name, and they are just column, okay, and you can create
onboard table name, suppose like the department, okay, so the department, and now, here, it is
completely created, and just verify in this department table, so here, I can create for execute,
and you can see here, create for the three tables, so three column, first on the ID department,
and the employee side, okay, so here, in this session, I have completely created for the two
table for use for the post SQL for the data code, okay, so here, in this session is completely done,
and here, perfect overview of creating table in the post SQL, and some practical examples,
okay, so I hope you perfectly understand in this session, so thank you for watching, and happy coding,
okay.